当列表项被点击时  使用Android中的Toast来显示
When the list item is clicked, use Android's Toast mechanism to display
天气信息  Toast是用来显示消息的弹出框  几秒中之后
the weather forecast string. A Toast is a pop-up that displays a message for
就会自动消失  它对调试非常有帮助  用以直观的显示信息提示
a few seconds before fading out. It's particularly useful for debugging, where
且不改变应用程序的用户界面
it can be used as a way to indicate status visually without altering the app UI.
我们把它放在我们的ListView控件上  放在ForecastFragment这个类的
We're going to put our list view, set item click listener into forecast fragment
onCreateView()方法里  我们可以输入
inside of the on create view method. We'll just start typing
listView.setOnItemClickListener
listView.setOnItemClickListener and
剩下的让编译器自动填充  在这个方法的参数里
let the auto complete fill in the rest. Inside of this function,
我们添加一个点击事件监听  并且实例化它
we're going to add click listener, which we can instantiate in place. So
在这里我们就可以添加 Android Toast 代码让它显示了
here's where we can call the code in Android to display the Toast. So, now that
你已经知道在哪添加 Toast 代码了吧  看一下 Toast 的文档
you know where to place the Toast code, take a look at the Toast documentation.
点击天气信息的时候弹出来一个 Toast 提示
Add a Toast when the list item is clicked that contains the weather information.
你可以从 forecast adapter 天气适配器里拿到天气信息
Hint. You can get the forecast by getting an item from the forecast adapter,
把这部分代码也写到我们刚刚预留的位置
at the position given by the on item click listener.